Hey, it'll be fun. If you have the
guts, try sitting on the chair for a minute.
If you sit,
shopping is free. Hey [screaming voice] friend, I've written it down outside. I mean, sit on the chair for a minute. No matter what happens, don't get up. Just sit on the chair for a minute. Whatever you buy is free. Take it
brother, you've become a master. Uncle, get
ready, I'll take you the stuff for free.
Come brother,
one minute, one minute.
Listen carefully. There's one condition too. One minute.
First, if you get up, double the bill for the stuff.
Uncle, Jaljala has also come. Jaljala has come. If you do
n't get up, get ready, I'll take it for free.
Come brother, take it.
A rooster is stuck. The
stuff has come. Give me the chair. Pick it up.
Then
tear it. Don't get up. That's the
copy you stole.
Brother, do
n't get up. I gave you
500 rupees. I stole it. I gave you the
money. Do
n't get up. [Music]
Third and last chance, the chair. Come and take it. The
copy worth 5000,
but one second.
O jaane chal, look at the money, Bondal,
lift your chair,
hey, you are
not getting up, will you get up
[music]
Jai Jai [music] Shri Ram